http://russwicks.com/privacy/index.htm

Privacy & Copyright
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting the site of Russ Wicks.  By visiting the website of Russ Wicks, visitors are bound by the following privacy policy and legal terms of use effective on March 9, 2012.
Links
This site may provide links to other company sites for the convenience of visitors.  When these links are followed from this site, visitors should be advised to follow the privacy statements of any site before providing any personally identifiable information.
Policy Changes
This privacy policy may change from time to time.  Any changes will be available on this site and be made effective on the provided date.
Copyright
Copyright 2012 Worldpro Group, LLC.  All Rights Reserved. All text, images, graphics, animation, videos, music and other materials on this website are subject to the copyright and other intellectual property rights of Worldpro Group, LLC.  This applies whether or not a copyright notice is present on the materials.  These materials may not be reproduced, distributed, modified or reposted to other websites without the express written permission of Worldpro Group, LLC.
Notices
The information contained herein is designed to be as comprehensive and factual as possible. Worldpro Group, LLC. reserves the right, however, to make changes at any time, without notice.
Some links provided in this site may lead to sites furnished by independent site owners.  The information presented therein is the sole responsibility of those site owners.  Worldpro Group, LLC. has no control or responsibility for the content of independent sites and provides these links to its visitors for their convenience.
Biography •
Supercar •
Speed Records •
Motorsports •
Partners •
Multimedia •
Press •
Merchandise •
